### Samantha Brown

# **Technical Project Management**

Miami, FL (754) - 302 - 7148

samantha24.sb@gmail.com

LinkedIn

Technical project manager, who's efficient with data extraction and group facilitation, I deliver business value from common data sources such as Google Doc, Slides, and Sheets. I have over seven years of customer service centered experience that helps me utilize logic and encouragement when delivering the best results as planned. My interest in providing security in all possible forms will aid in creating a high functioning supportive environment.

### **Skills**

- Budget Management, Time Management, Stakeholder Management, Risk Management, Project Documentation
- Waterfall Methodologies, Agile Methodologies, Team Collaboration, Group Facilitation, Mediation
- System Development Life Cycle, Multitasking, Performance Tracking, Data Modeling, Video Production

## **Project**

### Sierra 2.0

- Presented the framework for a three six month website update with a five year maintenance period
- Utilized the agile values as the foundation for each phase to reinforce a strong project plan
- Software used: Google Doc, Google Sheets, Google Slides, Apple Notes, Zoom, and Repli.it

# **Experience**

Thinkful **Studied Technical Project Management**  Remote

- December 2020 Created multiple diagrams to demonstrate the project life cycle and the Systems Development Lifecycle
- Conducted mock performance reviews and created various project documents
- Learned industry best practices for frameworks, methodologies, and interpersonal skills
- Gained additional knowledge for facilitating meetings, conflict resolution, being a servant leader

**Securitas Security Guard** 

Kendall, FL August 2020 - Present

- Interact with a wide range of people and permit entry to the facility once guidelines were met
- Enforce store, state, and federal safety procedures and COVID-19 policies
- Maintain company data security while validating visitors and creating a supportive environment
- Complete multiple reports by recording observations, information, occurrences, and surveillance activities; interviewing witnesses when necessary

**Brosnan Security Security Guard** 

Kev Biscavne, FL

**December 2019 - July 2020** 

- Utilized an 8 condo digital repository quickly to check whether visitors needed to be verified prior to providing access to the property on the beach while ensuring the line stayed at a minimum length
- Print parking passesm monitored the property via the surveillance system, access control for pedestrians at the front and back of the property
- Completed daily activity reports, incident reports when needed, communicated with security for the building if systems went down or additional visitor verification was required

**Alorica** 

Cutler Bay, FL

### **Escalation Specialist**

August 2013 - December 2019

- Processed twenty plus escalated cases daily at 60 wpm in a fast paced interpersonal environment
- Trained and managed agents for the Pre-AP program, providing support to administrators with things such as the new onboarding procedures, testing policies, and tracking test materials
- Handled supervisor request and communicated with clients about unsolved escalated cases while meeting daily and weekly metrics

**Education** 

**Cleavans Protection Services** 

Miami. FL State Security License December 2018